the national security implications
of building models
that are essentially cognition
that are essentially intelligence
right I've called where
we're going with this
a country of geniuses
and a data center
right So imagine 100
million people smarter than
any Nobel Prize winner
and it's going to
be under the of
one country or
So I think this
is I think it's
you it's a bit
like you I don't
know like selling you
know nuclear weapons to
North Korea and you
oh yeah Boeing made
the case your friend
David Sachs is basically
arming the No
I wouldn't refer to
any particular people but
I would just say
that this particular policy
think you Akin to
Yeah it's not well
advised